One of the things
I would say is
that there are super
intelligences today and they're
basically large corporations right
They're smarter than any
human can be at
solving the problem of
shipping commerce at the
lowest possible cost or
making solar panels at
the lowest possible cost
or launching rockets at
And so there's really
high returns to intelligence
in this area which
I incentivizes us
to kind of the
right thing It's also
I think it's a
business that is more
stable than consumer We
don't need ads we
don't need large
numbers of free users
We can just very
directly create value right
There aren't all these
weird externalities of like
you're prioritizing engagement you're
prioritizing these other things
you're all this slop
We just make stuff
that people can use